Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files P-T, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files A
  - Subject Files R
    - Robinson, George H. (Box A-102, Folder 277)
      Photographer if identified: George H. Robinson
    - Robinson, Gertrude (Box A-102, Folder 278)
      Photographer if identified: Bob Olen, Inge Hardison, Dummett, Campbell's Studios
    - Robinson, Gil (Box A-102, Folder 279)
      Print has stapled press release (four leaves) attached with paperclip.
    - Robinson, Gilbert A. (Box A-102, Folder 280)
      Four prints have single-leaf typescript press releases attached; also one stapled press release (two leaves).
      Photographer if identified: Florian DeNarde Studio
    - Robinson, Gloria E. (Box A-102, Folder 281)
    - Malcolm King-Harlem College Ext. (Box A-102, Folder 282)
      One newspaper clipping found loose in box.
    - Robinson, Gwendolyn (Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 1)
    - Robinson, H.L. (Box A-103, Folder 2)
    - Robinson, Hamilton (Box A-103, Folder 3)
      Also one velox print; one stapled typescript press release (two leaves) loose in folder; one manila envelope with typescript caption loose in folder.
    - Robinson, Harry A. (Box A-103, Folder 4)
      One print has typescript leaf description adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Bill Shurtleff
    - Robinson, Helen (Box A-103, Folder 5)
    - Robinson, Herbert N. (Bishop) (Box A-103, Folder 6)
      Photographer if identified: TWA
    - Robinson, Herman (Dr.) (Box A-103, Folder 7)
    - Robinson, Hilyard R. (Box A-103, Folder 8)
    - Robinson, Henry S. (Dr.) (Box A-103, Folder 9)
    - Robinson, Howard (Box A-103, Folder 10)
    - Robinson, Howard T. (Box A-103, Folder 11)
    - Robinson, Hugh (Box A-103, Folder 12)
      Print has single-leaf typescript caption attached.
    - Robinson, Ike (Box A-103, Folder 13)
      Photographer if identified: Official Photograph Board of Education
    - Robinson, Iris (Box A-103, Folder 14)
    - Robinson, Isaiah (Box A-103, Folder 15)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos, Harris Photo, TWA
    - Robinson, Lisa (Box A-103, Folder 16)
    - Robinson, Rachel (Box A-103, Folder 17)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Shelley Brown, Harris Photo
    - Robinson, J. Raymond (Box A-103, Folder 18)
      Photographer if identified: Jerry Soalt
    - Robinson, Jack (Box A-103, Folder 19)
    - Robinson, James (Box A-103, Folder 20)
    - Robinson, James E. (Box A-103, Folder 21)
      Two prints have single-leaf typescript press releases attached with paperclips.
    - Robinson, James (Lt.) (Box A-103, Folder 22)
    - Robinson, James S. (Box A-103, Folder 23)
    - Robinson, Jane (Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 24)
    - Robinson, Jackie (Box A-103, Folder 25)
    - Robinson, Jackie (Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 26)
      Note on folder: "+ Foundation." One print has single-leaf typescript attached.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, Cameron Studios, Town & Country, Monroe S. Frederick II
    - Robinson, Jackie (Mrs) (Box A-103, Folder 27)
      One print has single typescript leaf press release attached with paperclip; one has single-leaf typescript press release adhered on verso; one has single-leaf typescript description attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Taylor & Dull, James C. Campbell, Gill Photographers, Martha Swope, Pictorial Enterprise, Lensman
    - Robinson, Janice (Box A-103, Folder 28)
    - Robinson, Jean (Box A-103, Folder 29)
    - Robinson, Jean (Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 30)
      Photographer if identified: Arnold Hinten
    - Robinson, Jesse (Mayor) (Box A-103, Folder 31)
    - Robinson, Jim (Box A-103, Folder 32)
    - Robinson, Jo-Ann (Box A-103, Folder 33)
      Photographer if identified: Morgan Company
    - Robinson, John H. (Box A-103, Folder 34)
    - Robinson, John D. (Box A-103, Folder 35)
    - Robinson, John E. (Box A-103, Folder 36)
    - Robinson, John F. (Box A-103, Folder 37)
      One print has two newspaper clippings adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Ian Anderson
    - Robinson, John H. (Box A-103, Folder 38)
      Print is cut out and mounted on paper.
    - Robinson, Jonathan (Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 39)
    - Robinson, Joseph (Box A-103, Folder 40)
      Photographer if identified: Montague Everett
    - Robinson, Joseph B. (Dr.) (Box A-103, Folder 41)
    - Robinson, Jospeh (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 42)
    - Robinson, Joyce Gail (Box A-103, Folder 43)
    - Robinson, Julia (Box A-103, Folder 44)
    - Robinson, Julian K. (Box A-103, Folder 45)
    - Robinson, June G. (Box A-103, Folder 46)
      Print has typescript leaf press release (two leaves) attached with staple on border.
    - Robinson, Junius (Bob) (Box A-103, Folder 47)
    - Robinson, Katherine (Box A-103, Folder 48)
    - Robinson, Kelly (Box A-103, Folder 49)
    - Robinson, Kenneth B. (Box A-103, Folder 50)
    - Robinson, L.M. (Rev.) (Box A-103, Folder 51)
    - Robinson, Layhmond (Box A-103, Folder 52)
    - Robinson, Leon (Box A-103, Folder 53)
    - Robinson, Leon P. (Box A-103, Folder 54)
    - Robinson, Leslie (Box A-103, Folder 55)
      One print has single-leaf typescript description adhered on verso.
    - Roberts, Lillian (Box A-103, Folder 56)
    - Robinson, Lillie M. (Box A-103, Folder 57)
    - Robinson, Lois (Box A-103, Folder 58)
      Print has two typescript leaf descriptions attached with paperclip.
    - Robinson, Lorenzo (Rev. + Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 59)
    - Robinson, Louise (Box A-103, Folder 60)
    - Robinson, Louvinia (Box A-103, Folder 61)
    - Robinson, Luana (Box A-103, Folder 62)
    - Robinson, Lucia (Box A-103, Folder 63)
    - Robinson, Luis (Box A-103, Folder 64)
    - Robinson, M.E. (Box A-103, Folder 65)
    - Robinson, Mabel (Box A-103, Folder 66)
    - Robinson, Mallie (Box A-103, Folder 67)
    - Robinson, Mamie Davis (Box A-103, Folder 68)
    - Robinson, Margie (Box A-103, Folder 69)
    - Robinson, Marilyn (Box A-103, Folder 70)
      Photographer if identified: Curt Clemons Foto
    - Robinson, Martha (Box A-103, Folder 71)
    - Robinson, Mary (Box A-103, Folder 72)
    - Robinson, Matt (Box A-103, Folder 73)
    - Robinson, Maude E. (Box A-103, Folder 74)
    - Robinson, Maurice (Box A-103, Folder 75)
    - Robinson, Max (Box A-103, Folder 76)
    - Robinson, Milton B. (Rev.) (Box A-103, Folder 77)
    - Robinson, Moe (Box A-103, Folder 78)
      One print has single-leaf typescript description attached with staples on border.
    - Robinson, Morris (Box A-103, Folder 79)
    - Robinson, Nathaniel (Box A-103, Folder 80)
    - Robinson, Noel (Box A-103, Folder 81)
      Print has staple through image.
    - Robinson, Orezel R. (Dr.) (Box A-103, Folder 82)
    - Robinson, Pablo (Box A-103, Folder 83)
    - Robinson, Patricia (Box A-103, Folder 84)
    - Robinson, Paul (Lt.) (Box A-103, Folder 85)
    - Robinson, Patsy (Box A-103, Folder 86)
    - Robinson, Paul (Box A-103, Folder 87)
    - Robinson, Paul R. (Box A-103, Folder 88)
    - Robinson, Prezell (Box A-103, Folder 89)
      One print has single-leaf typescript press releases attached with staple on border; one print has single-leaf typescript press release attached with paperclip.
    - Robinson, Primus (Box A-103, Folder 90)
    - Robinson, Randall (Box A-103, Folder 91)
    - Robinson, Rachel (Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 92)
      Note on folder: "See Robinson, Jackie Mrs.."
    - Robinson, Ray (Box A-103, Folder 93)
      Note on folder: "See Robinson, Sugar Ray."
    - Robinson, Ray Jr. (Box A-103, Folder 94)
      Photographer if identified: Seymour S. Zolotorofe
    - Robinson, Raymond (Box A-103, Folder 95)
      Note on folder: "Jesse Walker's Son."
    - Robinson, Raymond (Box A-103, Folder 96)
    - Robinson, Raymond (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 97)
      Photographer if identified: Monroe S. Frederick II, Harris Photo
    - Robinson, Rebecca (Box A-103, Folder 98)
    - Robinson, Rekki (Box A-103, Folder 99)
    - Robinson, Richard A. (Sugarlips) (Box A-103, Folder 100)
      Both prints have single-leaf typescript captions attached. Stapled typescript press release (three leaves) loose in folder.
      Photographer if identified: A.I.D. (Agency for International Development)
    - Robinson, Archbishop Richard G. (Box A-103, Folder 101)
    - Robinson, Rita (Box A-103, Folder 102)
    - Robinson, Robert (Box A-103, Folder 103)
    - Robinson, Robert E. (Box A-103, Folder 104)
    - Robinson, Rob (Box A-103, Folder 105)
    - Robinson, Roger (Box A-103, Folder 106)
      Also one velox print. One print has single-leaf typescript press release adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Martha Swope, Richard Milani
    - Robinson, Roger (Box A-103, Folder 107)
    - Robinson, Ronald B. (Box A-103, Folder 108)
    - Robinson, Ronnie (Box A-103, Folder 109)
    - Robinson, Roscoe (Box A-103, Folder 110)
    - Robinson, S.W. (Judge) (Box A-103, Folder 111)
    - Robinson, Sampson (Box A-103, Folder 112)
    - Robinson, Samuel (Sonny) (Box A-103, Folder 113)
    - Robinson, Sandra (Box A-103, Folder 114)
    - Robinson, Sharon (Box A-103, Folder 115)
    - Robinson, Sheila (Box A-103, Folder 116)
    - Robinson, Shirley (Box A-103, Folder 117)
    - Robinson, Smokey (Box A-103, Folder 118)
      Also one velox print; two prints have single-leaf typescript press releases attached.
    - Robinson, Sonny (Box A-103, Folder 119)
    - Robinson, Sophia D. (Box A-103, Folder 120)
    - Robinson, Spottswood W. (Box A-103, Folder 121)
      Stapled typescript leaf press release (two leaves) loose in folder.
    - Robinson, Sylvia (Box A-103, Folder 122)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo
    - Robinson, Sugar Ray (Box A-103, Folder 123)
    - Robinson, Sullivan (Box A-103, Folder 124)
      Also one velox print. One print has newspaper clipping adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Bert Andrews, Allen Morgan
    - Robinson, Thelma (Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 125)
      Note on folder: "See Gracie M. George."
      Photographer if identified: Neil De Angelis
    - Robinson, Toy, Jr. (Box A-103, Folder 126)
    - Robinson, Vance (Box A-103, Folder 127)
    - Robinson, Vernon (Box A-103, Folder 128)
    - Robinson, Vicki Sue (Box A-103, Folder 129)
    - Robinson, W.L. (Rev. + Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 130)
    - Robinson, Walter (Box A-103, Folder 131)
    - Robinson, Wanda (Box A-103, Folder 132)
    - Robinson, Vivian (Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 133)
    - Robinson, Will (Box A-103, Folder 134)
    - Robinson, William (Box A-103, Folder 135)
    - Robinson, Wiliam (Box A-103, Folder 136)
    - Robinson, Wm. Rev. (Box A-103, Folder 137)
    - Robinson, William (Box A-103, Folder 138)
    - Robinson, William (Box A-103, Folder 139)
      Photographer if identified: B.F. Goodrich
    - Robinson, Wm. (Bishop) (Box A-103, Folder 140)
    - Robinson, William A. (Box A-103, Folder 141)
    - Robinson, William E. (Box A-103, Folder 142)
    - Robinson, William H. (Box A-103, Folder 143)
    - Robinson, William J. (Box A-103, Folder 144)
    - Robinson, Wm. P., Sr. (Box A-103, Folder 145)
    - Robinson, Zack (Box A-103, Folder 146)
    - Robinson-Jackson, Barbara (Box A-103, Folder 147)
    - Robles, Benny (Box A-103, Folder 148)
    - Robles, Paul (Box A-103, Folder 149)
    - Robles, Victor (Box A-103, Folder 150)
      Photographer if identified: Hamilton Associates, Dave Greene Photo
    - Roby, Jasper (Box A-103, Folder 151)
      Also one velox print and one newspaper clipping loose in folder.
    - Rock City Band (Box A-103, Folder 152)
    - Roch, George (Box A-103, Folder 153)
    - Rocch, Max (Box A-103, Folder 154)
    - Rochan, Romero (Box A-103, Folder 155)
      Print has four images and staple on border.
    - Rochdale Negro Cultural Society (Box A-103, Folder 156)
    - Rochdale Village (Box A-103, Folder 157)
    - Roche, Betty (Box A-103, Folder 158)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, James C. Powell
    - Roche, Betty (Box A-103, Folder 159)
    - Rochelle, Carlton (Dr.) (Box A-103, Folder 160)
      Print has typescript press release (four leaves) attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Lane Bros.
    - Rochelle, James (Box A-103, Folder 161)
    - Rochester, Chas. W. (Box A-103, Folder 162)
      Photographer if identified: Wilson
    - Rochester, Marjorie (Box A-103, Folder 163)
    - Rochelle, James (Box A-103, Folder 164)
    - Rock, Jerome (Box A-103, Folder 165)
    - Rock, Edwin (Box A-103, Folder 166)
    - Rock, Harriet (Box A-103, Folder 167)
      Staple on border.
    - Rock, Ira (Box A-103, Folder 168)
    - Rock, Linda (Box A-103, Folder 169)
    - Rock, Rubin J. (Box A-103, Folder 170)
    - Rock Testament (Box A-103, Folder 171)
    - Rockaway Revue Performers Foundation Of Youth (Box A-103, Folder 172)
    - Rockefeller Center Building (Box A-103, Folder 173)
      Pint has single-leaf typescript description attached.
    - Rockefeller, David (Box A-103, Folder 174)
      Also one velox print. Two prints have single-leaf typescript letters attached with paperclips; one has single-leaf typescript press release attached.
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen Studio, Big M Photo Studio, Jan Jachniewicz, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Rockefeller, John D. (Box A-103, Folder 175)
      Photographer if identified: Arnold Newman
    - Rockefeller, Laurance (Box A-103, Folder 176)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 177)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix and one velox print with caption.
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Arnold Newman
    - Rockefeller, Laurance (Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 178)
      Print has single-leaf typescript description attached on verso.
    - Rockefeller, Nelson (Box A-103, Folder 179)
      Photographer if identified: George West, Bert Smith, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Rockefeller, Plaza (Box A-103, Folder 180)
    - Rockefeller, Rodman (Box A-103, Folder 181)
      Also one velox print. One print has typescript press release (two leaves) attached; one typescript press release (two leaves) loose in folder.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, James W. B. Burke
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop (Box A-103, Folder 182)
      Also five negatives (eight images total). One print has single-leaf typescript press release attached with paperclips.
      Photographer if identified: David Hawkins, Roosevelt S. Zander
    - Rockets (Box A-103, Folder 183)
    - Rocky "G" (Box A-103, Folder 184)
    - Rocky's Stars (Box A-103, Folder 185)
    - Rocky's Starletts (Box A-103, Folder 186)
      Photographer if identified: Big M Photo Service
    - Rocquemore, Helen (Box A-103, Folder 187)
      Photographer if identified: Al Burley, Allen Morgan, James Gilbert
    - Racourt, Margaret (Box A-103, Folder 188)
    - Rodda, Donald (Box A-103, Folder 189)
    - Rodell, Barbara (Box A-103, Folder 190)
    - Rodeo (Box A-103, Folder 191)
    - Rodfield, Flora (Box A-103, Folder 192)
    - Rodgers, Andre (Box A-103, Folder 193)
    - Rodges, Carol Ruth (Box A-103, Folder 194)
      Photographer if identified: Monclova
    - Rodgers, Coleman (Box A-103, Folder 195)
    - Rodgers, Frederick (Box A-103, Folder 196)
    - Rodgers, Johnny (Box A-103, Folder 197)
      One print has typescript description attached.
    - Rodgers, Jonathan (Box A-103, Folder 198)
    - Rodgers, Mary (Box A-103, Folder 199)
      Photographer if identified: Walter Barringer
    - Rodgers, Nile (Box A-103, Folder 200)
    - Rodgers, Ralph Hugo (Box A-103, Folder 201)
    - Rodgers, Robin (Box A-103, Folder 202)
    - Rodgers, Rod Dance Co. (Box A-103, Folder 203)
      Photographer if identified: John Gallazi
    - Rodgers, Russell (Box A-103, Folder 204)
    - Rodgers, Theo. C. (Box A-103, Folder 205)
    - Rodgers, Yvonne (Dee Dee) (Box A-103, Folder 206)
    - Rodino, Peter (Box A-103, Folder 207)
    - Rodney, Carl (Box A-103, Folder 208)
      Photographer if identified: Lloyd Patterson
    - Rodney, Michael (Box A-103, Folder 209)
    - Rodriguez, Bobby (Box A-103, Folder 210)
    - Rodney, Walter (Dr.) (Box A-103, Folder 211)
    - Rodney, Ronald (Box A-103, Folder 212)
    - Rodriguez, Frank (Box A-103, Folder 213)
    - Rodriguez, Hazel U. (Box A-103, Folder 214)
    - Rodriguez, John (Box A-103, Folder 215)
    - Rodriguez, Laura (Box A-103, Folder 216)
    - Rodriguez, Lynn (Box A-103, Folder 217)
      Print is mounted on paper.
    - Rodriguez, Marta (Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 218)
    - Rodriguez, Robert (Box A-103, Folder 219)
    - Roe, Helene (Box A-103, Folder 220)
    - Roe, Wendell P. (Box A-103, Folder 221)
    - Roebuck, Carolyn (Box A-103, Folder 222)
    - Roebuck, Elizabeth (Box A-103, Folder 223)
    - Roebuck, Waldemar E. (Box A-103, Folder 224)
      Photographer if identified: Pontificia Photographia, David McAdams
    - Roebuck, William (Box A-103, Folder 225)
    - Roffman, Dorothy (Box A-103, Folder 226)
      Folder notes "See Donna Canton."
    - Rogalin, Wilma (Box A-103, Folder 227)
    - Rogan, F. Capt. (Box A-103, Folder 228)
    - Roger, David (Box A-103, Folder 229)
      One velox print (two images total).
    - Rogers, Adelaide Mrs. (Box A-103, Folder 230)
    - Rogers, Arthur (Box A-103, Folder 231)
      Note on folder: "See Newbold Morris."
    - Rogers, Arthur J. (Box A-103, Folder 232)
      Also one velox print and one paper stereotype matrix.
      Photographer if identified: Studio of The New York Times, Conway Studios Corp.
    - Rogers, Bill (Box A-103, Folder 233)
    - Rogers, Bob (Box A-103, Folder 234)
    - Rogers, Bobby (Box A-103, Folder 235)
    - Rogers, Charles C. (Maj. Gen.) (Box A-103, Folder 236)
    - Rogers, D. (Box A-103, Folder 237)
    - Rogers, D. J. (Box A-103, Folder 238)
    - Roger, David (Box A-103, Folder 239)
    - Rogers, Denise (Box A-103, Folder 240)
    - Rogers, Diana (Box A-103, Folder 241)
    - Rogers, Dorothy (Box A-103, Folder 242)
    - Rogers, Ernest (Box A-103, Folder 243)
      Print is mounted on board.
    - Rogers, Frank S. (Box A-103, Folder 244)
    - Rogers, Fred (Box A-103, Folder 245)
    - Rogers, George B. (Box A-103, Folder 246)
    - Rogers, Ginger (Box A-103, Folder 247)
      Both prints have single-leaf typescript press releases attached.
    - Rodgers, Griffin (Dr.) (Box A-103, Folder 248)
    - Rogers, Hubert A. (Archbishop) (Box A-103, Folder 249)
      Note on folder: "North American Catholic Church."
    - Rogers, S.A. (Box A-103, Folder 250)
    - Rogers, Jaime (Box A-103, Folder 251)
      Print has single-leaf typescript caption on verso.
    - Rogers, Jean (Box A-103, Folder 252)
    - Rogers, Jean (Box A-103, Folder 253)
      Also one photocopy in envelope.
    - Rogers, Joel A. (Box A-103, Folder 254)
      This folder is empty. Note on folder: "See Negro Heritage Library."
    - Rogers, John E. (Sr.) (Box A-103, Folder 255)
      Photographer if identified: Capitol Studios
    - Rogers, Kenny & Marianne (Box A-103, Folder 256)
      Also two stapled typescript press releases (one five leaves, one two leaves) loose in folder.
    - Rogers, Lafayette W. (Rev.) (Box A-103, Folder 257)
    - Rodgers, Lee (Box A-103, Folder 258)
    - Rogers, Levi-Roy (Box A-103, Folder 259)
    - Rogers, Lillian (Box A-103, Folder 260)
    - Rogers, Marie (Box A-103, Folder 261)
    - Rogers, Marita (Box A-103, Folder 262)
      Note on folder: "See James Brown."
    - Rogers, Mary (Mrs.) (Box A-103, Folder 263)
    - Rogers, Morton (Box A-103, Folder 264)
      Photographer if identified: Louise Wise Services
    - Rogers, Nathaniel (Box A-103, Folder 265)
    - Rogers, Olivia (Box A-103, Folder 266)
    - Rogers, Patricia (Box A-103, Folder 267)
    - Rogers, Patricia (Box A-103, Folder 268)
    - Rogers, R.R. (Bishop) (Box A-103, Folder 269)
    - Rogers, Ralph (Dr.) (Box A-103, Folder 270)
    - Rogers, Richard (Box A-103, Folder 271)
    - Rogers, Rod Dance Company (Box A-103, Folder 272)
      Also three velox prints, one computer-printed color poster and one stapled typescript essay (three leaves) and a single-leaf typescript press release loose in folder.
      Photographer if identified: Van Williams, Rod Rodgers Dance Co., Bill Longcare,
    - Rodgers, Rod (Box A-103, Folder 273)
      Also four velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Bill Longcore, Siehl Ko
    - Rogers, Monica (Box A-103, Folder 274)
    - Rogers, Joseph J. (Box A-104, Folder 1)
    - Rogers, Ross (See Leon Coleman) (Box A-104, Folder 2)
    - Rogers, Ralph H. Jr. Dr. (Box A-104, Folder 3)
    - Rogers, Robin (Box A-104, Folder 4)
    - Rogers, Russell (Box A-104, Folder 5)
      Photographer if identified: Leon Bolden
    - Rogers, Timmie (Box A-104, Folder 6)
      Also one velox print. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Weldon A. McDougal III, Al Naidoff, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Donald L. Miller, Bro. David McAdams, James J. Kriegsmann, United Press International,
    - Rogers, Walter A. (Box A-104, Folder 7)
    - Rogers, William D. (Box A-104, Folder 8)
      Photographer if identified: US Agency for International Development
    - Rogers, Wm. P. Secretary of State (Box A-104, Folder 9)
    - Rogers, Willie Carl (Box A-104, Folder 10)
    - Rogers, Wilton (Box A-104, Folder 11)
      Also one ms. note.
    - Rogerson, Charlette (Box A-104, Folder 12)
      Photographer if identified: Burley Photo Service
    - Rogoff, Bernard (Box A-104, Folder 13)
      One paper stereotype matrix and one halftone print.
    - Rogiers, Arnett (Box A-104, Folder 14)
    - Rogosin, Lionel (Box A-104, Folder 15)
    - Rohan, Nanette (Box A-104, Folder 16)
    - Rohan, Thomas E. (Box A-104, Folder 17)
    - Rohlehr, John (Box A-104, Folder 18)
    - Rohlsen, Henry Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-104, Folder 19)
    - Rohlsen, Wm. (Box A-104, Folder 20)
    - Roisman, Charles (Box A-104, Folder 21)
      1 print is of Nanette Rohan.
    - Rojas, Don (Box A-104, Folder 22)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, Peterkin Photo,
    - Rojas, Robert (Box A-104, Folder 23)
    - Roker, Renny (Box A-104, Folder 24)
    - Roker, Roxie (Box A-104, Folder 25)
      Also 2 velox prints. 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Bert Andrews, Patrick Owens, Maurice Seymour, Ace Creative Photos
    - Roker, Wally & Renny (Box A-104, Folder 26)
    - Rolan, Leonard Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-104, Folder 27)
    - Roland, James (Box A-104, Folder 28)
    - Roland, Johnny (Box A-104, Folder 29)
    - Rolander, C. A. (Box A-104, Folder 30)
    - Rollan, Rosetta (Box A-104, Folder 31)
    - Rolle, Esther (Box A-104, Folder 32)
    - Rolle, Esther (Box A-104, Folder 33)
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene, Glen Frieson,
    - Rolle, Harry (Box A-104, Folder 34)
      Polaroid print taped to cardboard, with staple.
    - Rolle, LaVerne (Box A-104, Folder 35)
    - Rolle, Marian (Box A-104, Folder 36)
      Photographer if identified: Kees De Graaff, Marilyn McClaren
    - Rolle, Tony (Box A-104, Folder 37)
      Photographer if identified: Marian Fletcher Croson
    - Rollerson, Charles (Box A-104, Folder 38)
    - Rolby, Aron L. (Box A-104, Folder 39)
      Photographer if identified: Marty Cobin
    - Rolling, Ollie (Box A-104, Folder 40)
    - Rollings, Bob (Box A-104, Folder 41)
    - Rollings, Eva (Box A-104, Folder 42)
    - Rollins, Mr. (See Mr. Bonner) (Box A-104, Folder 43)
    - Rollins, Bryant (Box A-104, Folder 44)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Merrill Roberts, Tyrone Dukes, Monroe S. Frederick,
    - Rollins, Bryant (Box A-104, Folder 45)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Merrill Roberts,
    - Rollins, Charlamae H. (Box A-104, Folder 46)